export const quizData = [
    {
        id : 1,
        question : 'Which one of the following river flows between Vindhyan and Satpura ranges?',
        option :{
            optionlist : ['Narmada', 'Mahanadi', 'Son', 'Netravati'],
            correctanswer : 'Narmada'
        }
    },
    {
        id : 2,
        question : 'The Central Rice Research Station is situated in?',
        option :{
            optionlist : ['Chennai', 'Cuttack', 'Bangalore', 'Quilon'],
            correctanswer : 'Cuttack'
        }
    },
    {
        id : 3,
        question : 'Who among the following wrote Sanskrit grammar?',
        option :{
            optionlist : ['Kalidasa', 'Charak', 'Panini', 'Aryabhatt'],
            correctanswer : 'Panini'
        }
    },
    {
        id : 4,
        question : ' Which among the following headstreams meets the Ganges in last?',
        option :{
            optionlist : ['Alaknanda', 'Pindar', 'Mandakini', 'Bhagirathi'],
            correctanswer : 'Bhagirathi'
        }
    },
    {
        id : 5,
        question : 'The metal whose salts are sensitive to light is?',
        option :{
            optionlist : ['Zinc', 'Silver', 'Copper', 'Aluminum'],
            correctanswer : 'Silver'
        }
    },
    {
        id : 6,
        question : ' Patanjali is well known for the compilation of â€“',
        option :{
            optionlist : ['Yoga Sutra', 'Panchatantra', ' Brahma Sutra', 'Ayurveda'],
            correctanswer : 'Yoga Sutra'
        }
    },
    {
        id : 7,
        question : 'River Luni originates near Pushkar and drains into which one of the following?',
        option :{
            optionlist : ['Rann of Kachchh', 'Arabian Sea', 'Gulf of Cambay', 'Lake Sambhar'],
            correctanswer : 'Rann of Kachchh'
        }
    },
    {
        id : 8,
        question : 'Which one of the following rivers originates in Brahmagiri range of Western Ghats?',
        option :{
            optionlist : ['Pennar', 'Cauvery', 'Krishna', 'Tapti'],
            correctanswer : 'Cauvery'
        }
    },
    {
        id : 9,
        question : 'The country that has the highest in Barley Production?',
        option :{
            optionlist : ['China', 'India', 'Russia', 'France'],
            correctanswer : 'Russia'
        }
    },
    {
        id : 10,
        question : 'Tsunamis are not caused by',
        option :{
            optionlist : ['Hurricanes', 'Earthquakes', 'Undersea landslides', 'Volcanic eruptions'],
            correctanswer : 'Hurricanes'
        }
    },
]